

(404) 820-4106 |

ieratlee@gmail.com |

interatlee github.io | interatlee

Data analyst with 4 years experience in analyzing, mapping, and troubleshooting data in business and academic settings. Comfortable communicating to technical and non-technical audiences through the creation of visual dashboard and written documentation. Worked closely with a variety of stakeholders to establish proper expectations and deliver accurate results. Experience manipulating large data sets to inform data-driven decisions.

Technical Skills

SQL, Python, R, Javascript, Matlab, Java, C, D3.js, Angular.js, Markdown, HTML5, CSS

Looker, Tableau, Redshift, MySQL, Agile, Git, Jira, Segment, DBT, Jupyter Notebook, Scikit-Learn, Pandas, MongoDB, **Tools** UNIX, Linux, Windows, Mac OS

Experience _

Aceable, Inc Austin, TX

ANALYTICS SPECIALIST Jul 2019 - March 2021

- Gathered reporting requirements, documented, and communicated project progress with stakeholders across 5 departments
- Created dashboards to analyze sales metrics across various departments (Looker, Segment, Redshift)
- Created reporting and alerting infrastructure for accurate monthly payouts to to over 50 business development partners
- · Maintained and improved first and last touch marketing attribution models to track sales by marketing channel
- Performed quality assurance testing on email marketing data to ensure accurate tracking through the data pipelines
- Troubleshoot time-sensitive data issues and and communicated resolutions

National University of Singapore Lee Kuan Yew School of Public Policy

Singapore

RESEARCH ASSOCIATE - DR. YOU-NA LEE

Mar 2018 - May 2019

- Project: Measure design novelty with patent based indicators
- Created quantitative measure of innovation in US design patents from over 500,000 patents (Python, SQL)
- Analyzed patent trends over a 35 year period showing 12% increase in design activity in technological industries (Python, Pandas)
- Documented methods of data collection and analysis for an academic paper

Georgia Tech Research Institute

Atlanta, GA

RESEARCH INTERN May 2017 - Feb 2018

- Developed 20 year economic forecast model to predict market demand of materials across the US on a small team (R)
- Created interactive data visualizations and dashboards for monitoring price indices and determining outlier performance (Tableau)
- Major contributor to development of database in MEAN stack web application (MongoDB)
- Applied machine learning algorithms, SVN and KNN, to child welfare data to predict patient outcomes (Python, Sci-kit learn)

Eaton Corporation

Peachtree City, GA

SOFTWARE ENGINEER INTERN

May 2016 - Aug 2016

- Developed, tested, and internationalized code for hybrid-mobile application to configure commercial lighting (Angular, is, Ionic)
- Created user stories and UI mockups that directed development (Jira)
- Supported accelerated development by 20%

Education _

Georgia Institute of Technology

Atlanta, GA

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE WITH HONORS

Dec 2017

- · Concentrations: Modeling and Simulation, Media
- Faculty Honors 4.0 Semester
- Fall 2015 Benjamin A. Gilman International Scholar
- · Semester abroad in at The Chinese University of Hong Kong in Hong Kong, China

Mentoring _

Freelance Tutoring

ADULT AND YOUTH ESL TUTOR

Singapore

Mar 2018- Mar 2019

- Created individualized weekly lesson plans for 8 students of various ages
- Collaborated with the student's parents to create practical learning goals and monitor performance